紐約州 洛克波特
你個混蛋
You son of a bitch!
- 他咬你了? - 是的 行了 你給我別動
- Did he bite you? - Yeah. All right,don't move.
Dale schrader 我們現在以謀殺Stacy Ryan
Dale schrader, you're under arrest for the murder of stacy ryan
和綁架自己女兒Jennny的罪名逮捕你
and the kidnapping of your daughter jenny.
聽著 我們抓到他了 不 我怕 我要見我媽媽
Listen,we got him. No,i'm afraid. Please let me see my mom.
- 她在哪? - 現在不行 她會在醫院跟我們會合
- No,your mom-- Your mom,she's gonna meet us at the hospital. - Where is she?
- 他沒法傷害你了 你沒事了 - 讓我跟她道個別
- And he cannot hurt you. You're gonna be fine. - Let me sayood-bye to her.
從你綁架她的那一刻開始 你就沒這個權利了
You lost that right the minute you took her.
- 她將會... - 她是我女兒
- She's gonna be-- - She's my daughter.
Jenny
Jenny.
別 別 不用怕 沒事了 他傷害不了你的
No,no,it's ok. It's ok. He can't hurt you.
Jenny 對不起
Jenny. I'm sorry.
- 你和她一起去醫院? - 沒錯 我來吧
- You gonna ride in with her? - Yeah,i got it.
Jenny 聽我說 我保證 他很長時間都不會再出現了
Jenny,listen to me. I promise you he's gonna go away for a long time.
一切都會好的
It's gonna be all right.
Morgan會等救護車過來 我和Bunting帶他去局
Morgan's gonna wait for the ambulance. Bunting and I are taking him in.
是的--不 屋堥S人 他剛離開...
Yeah--no,the cabin's empty. He just left...
- 好的 解除安珀警報 - 收到 卡車查過了麼?
- Yeah, cancel the aer alert. - Roger that. Truck recovered?
查過了 沒問題
Negative on the truck.
女孩很害怕 但應該沒什麼大事
The girl's upset, but she ses ok.
Morgan探員會帶她過去
Agent morgan is gonna bring her in.
他會跟隨救護車一道送她過去 幾分鐘之後就出發
He's gonna escort her in the ambulance. They should be leaving in a couple minutes.
是的 我們找到她了 跟你媽媽說說話?
Yeah,we got her. You want to talk to your mom?
媽媽? 不 我沒事 我發誓
Mom? No,i'm ok. I promise.
隨機殺了個女人 然後綁架了自己的孩子
Killed aandom woman and kidnapped his kid.
使用同一輛卡車 可不是明智之舉啊
Used the same truck. Not the brightest bulb.
他被關了11年 必然疏於實踐
He's been locked up for 11 years. He's out of practice.
不是說這種人反而會變得更強麼?
Dot they say these guys come out better criminals?
- 那是說聰明的人 - 你是說我笨麼?
- Smart ones do. - You saying I'm dumb?
你沒有耐心 很憤怒
You're impatient,angry.
你把孩子搶來 只是為了報復前妻
You took your own kid just to get backt your ex.
你倒是很清楚
You got it all figured out.
- 你的前妻說... - 她在說謊 我真該殺了她
- Well,your ex-wife said-- - she was a liar.And I should have killed her.
就像殺死Stacy Ryan一樣?
Like you killed stacy ryan?
你為什麼要這麼做呢?
Why did yodo it?
- 你不會理解的 - 那你倒是說說看
- You wouldn't understand. - Try me.
- 這就是我不能理解這傢伙的地方 - 是什麼?
- Here's what I don't get about this guy. - What's that?
他之前一直是個小偷 出監獄之後卻成了殺人犯
His whole life he's a thief, he comes out of prison a murderer.
- 他殺害了一個無辜的女人 - 你怎麼知道她是無辜的?
- He killed an innocent won. - How do you know she's innocent?
你捅死了她 把她從卡車堨等X來
You stabbed her and threw herout of.
她能對你做什麼?
What the hell did she ever do to you?
我就不明白了 你咋就不能珍惜現在的自由呢
You know, what I don't get is why you couldn't just appreciate the freedom.
你可以一直住在那個小屋 享受安靜的生活
You could have holed up in that cabin a long time, enjoyed the quiet.
可有人就是這麼不安分
But some people just need the distractions.
估計是被關太久 關得快發瘋了
You probably got used to all that madness when you were locked up.
小羊羔去跟大灰狼討論和平共處 這才叫發瘋呢
It's madness for the sheep to talk peace with a wolf.
你這像是我爸爸說出來的話
You that soundst used to alike somethings whenmy daddy would say.
- Thomas Fuller (17世紀歷史學家 教士) - 覺得我不賴吧?
- Thomas fuller. - You impressed?
我只很驚訝 這麼說 你是大灰狼了
I'm surprised. So you're the wolf.
- 你不會知道的 - 又來了 還是那麼自負
- You have no idea. - There it is. That ego.
你知道 有那麼一下 你還真叫人難以預測
You know, for one second, you were unpredictable.
但你忍不住 你總是要去"一鳴驚人"
But you can'help yourself. You gotta talk a big talk.
這麼做也太無聊了
But just so you know, that's boring.
嘿 怎麼了? 坐直了
Hey,what was that? sit up.
- 哦 我一定是病了 - 什麼情況?
- Oh,i'm gonna be sick. - What's going on?
- 我不知道 - 我把車停一邊去
- I don't know. - I'm gonna pu over.
- 哦 我一定是生病了 - 你能把車燈打開麼?
Oh,i'm gonna be sick. - can you turn the light on?
- 我一定是病了 - 噢 到底怎麼回事?
- I'm nna be sick. - Oh,what the hell?
- 我還是那麼無聊麼? - 什麼?
- Am I still ring? - What?
你還是覺得我無聊麼?
Am I boring?
犯罪心理 第五季 第11集 復仇
Criminal Minds Season05 Episode11 Retaliation
鑰匙在哪?
Where are the keys?
噢 等等 我是聯邦探員
Oh,wait! I'm a federal agent!
這有一個囚犯 剛剛殺死了一名警官
I have a prisoner in here who's just killed this officer!
我就知道 你個賤貨!
I knew it. You are one committed son of a bitch.
- 哦 我的胳膊 - 不 不 他是囚犯
- Oh,my arm! - No,no,that's the prisoner!
你在幹什麼?
What are youoing?
- 把槍給我 - 什麼 你怎麼回事?
- Give me the gun. - What? What's wrong with you?
你殺了個警察?
You killed a cop?
- 把槍給我 - 她是個條子
- Give me the gun. - He's a fed.
聽著 她已經知道我們有兩個人了
Look,she knows there's two of us now.
你需要縫針
You're gonna need stitches.
我不要去醫院
I'm not going to the hospital.
血流很多 壓住它
There's a lot of blood. Put pressure on it.
- 把槍給我 - 你會沒事的
- Give me the gun. - You're gonna be all right.
- 快點 給我槍 - 快點進卡車
- Come on, give me the damn gun! - Get in the truck!
快點
Come on!
"人類更願意報復傷害 而不願報答好意
"men are more ready to repay an injury than a benefit,
因為感恩就好比重擔 而復仇 則快感重重"
Because gratitude is a burden and revenge a pleasure."
塔西佗 (Tacitus 古羅馬元老院議員 歷史學家)
tacitus.
靠邊停 那是我們的人 靠邊
Pull over. That's o of us. Pull over.
Prentiss 發生什麼事了? 你還好嗎?
Prentiss! What the hell happened? Are you all right?
Bunting 在下面 他已經死了
Bunting's down there. He's dead.
- Schrader呢? - 他跑了
- Where's schrader? - He's gone.
是輛大...卡車 紐約的車牌
It was a--a big...Truck,new york tags,
呃 VA737
uh,victor alpha 737.
他們已經往北邊開了有10分鐘了
They went northbound about 10 minutes ago.
該死的 逃了
Son of a bitch got away.
他有同夥
He's got a partner.
回歸後的第一案 我們要是拿下 你就可以回家吃早飯咯
First case back,wwon, and you'll be home for breakfast.
我們一直不知道為什麼Schrader 要殺了Stacy Ryan
We never figured out why schrader killed stacy ryan.
她跟他的前妻和孩子沒有任何關係
She had no connection to his daughter or his ex-wife.
出事了 Emily在醫院 Bunting死了
There's been an accident. Emily's in the hospital, bunting's dead.
- 她沒事吧? - 腦震盪
- Is she all right? - She has a concussion.
- Morgan和她在一起嗎? - 是的
- Is morgan with her? - Yeah.
- Schrader呢? - 上了一輛卡車 朝北開去
- Where's schrader? - Northbound in a truck.
- 卡車? - 他有同夥
- A truck? - He has a partner.
- 什麼? - 得趕緊設路障 這就設
- What? - We need roadblocks--now.
有車牌號麼?
Do we have a tag?
- 呃 Emily 大概說了一部分 - 總比沒有好
- Uh,emily murmured a partial. - Better than nothing.
他可能往加拿大走了 我們需要熟悉這片區域的人
He could be headed to canada. We need somebody who knows the area.
我去找當地警察
I'll get an officer.
- 還有 JJ-- - 我明白 公佈Schrader照片 全城通緝
- And jj-- - Yeah,you want schrader's face everywhere.
Schrader曾經搶過銀行
Schrader was a bank robber.
現在他殺了一個女人 綁架自己的女兒 又殺了一個警察
Now he's murdered a woman, kidnapped his daughter, and killed a cop.
他顯然比我們之前想像的要複雜的多
He's obviously more sophisticated than we originally thought.
他有更大的計劃 不僅僅是帶著女兒逃到國外去
He's got a bigger plan. It's not just about getting his daughter and fleeing the country.
咱們的側寫 從沒出現他的同夥
We never profiled that he'd have a partner.
我們一點也不瞭解這個人
We don't know this guy at all.
你可比我想像的牛多啦
Got to admit you're better than I thought.
- 那幫笨蛋連什麼襲擊他們的都不知道 - 坐好了你
- Those idiots don't know what hit them. - Sit still.
至少給我點阿司匹林吧
At least give me some aspirin.
拜託 你還真下的了手?
Come on. Really?
哦 哥們 弄完沒 我們該走了
Oh,man. Are you done yet? We gotta go.
- 我手上沒鑰匙 - 什麼?
- I don't have the key. - What?
我接頭的人不在那 她8點上班
My contact wasn't there. Her shift starts at 8:00.
明天? 那我們只能等著了?
Tomorrow? So we're just gonna wait?
你知道麼 如果你沒殺那個警察 事情就不會這麼嚴重
You know,this wouldn't be such a big deal if you hadn't killed a cop.
噢 他沒完沒了地說話
Oh,he didn't know when to shut up.
知道接下來會怎麼著嗎?
You know what's gonna happen now?
大街小巷都會貼滿你的照片 增加兩倍警力巡邏
They're gonna put your picture everywhere.
你把你逃離這堛瑣鷛|都給搞砸了
You just screwed your chances of ever tting out of here.
好吧 看 這就是為啥把你拉進來了
Well,see,that's where you come in.
我相信你的
Got faith in you.
這會留疤麼?
Is this gonna leave a scar?
- 不 我們得找到Schrader - 有咱的人負責著呢
- No,we gotta find schrader. - The team's got it covered.
我不要待在這 我真的很好 趕緊把這車停了
Don't make me stay here. I'fine,honestly. Pull this thing over.
Prentiss 你都沒法集中精力 你摔得腦震盪了
Prentiss,you can't even focus. You have a concussion.
- 我看見那個人了 - 白人  四十多歲 我知道了
- I saw the guy. - White,40s,i know.
好吧 你給我做個認知測試
Ok,so give me a cognitive interview.
- 你腎上腺急速升高 - 肯定的啊
- Your adrenaline's pumping. - Exactly.
- Emily 你剛受了驚嚇 - 它突然就那麼發生了 我從未這麼清醒過
- Emily,you're in shock. - It just happened. It'll never be clearer.
- 你開了幾槍? - 3槍
- How many shots did you fire? - 3.
你子彈夾都打空了
You emptied your clip.
不... 真的嗎?
No... I did?
Schrader在90年代 參與了一系列的銀行搶劫
All right,so schrader pulled a series of bank heists in the 1990s.
是那些案子堸艉@一個 得了自由身的人
Was the only one to ever go away for the crimes.
他是個模範囚徒 判了15年 剛待11年就出來了
He was a model prisoner, on served 11 of his 15 years,
就是因為表現良好
Was released early on good behavior,
他那些朋友不是死了 就是還在監獄
and any friends he had are either dead or still in prison.
在事發地北邊 離加拿大不遠處 發現了一輛3噸的卡車
A 3-ton truck was found north of the accident, not too far from canada.
我們在邊境處部署了最強大的警力 他可能知道
We have the heaviest presence at border crossings. He probably knows that.
我覺得他不可能長時間坐得住
I don't think he's gonna sit still for long.
沒準不得不靜養 得根據他的傷勢來看
He might have to depending onow injured he is.
- 我們現在掌握了什麼? - Dale Schrader曾因搶劫入獄
- What do we know? - dale schrader went to prison for robbery.
他幹得很利落 所犯罪行都不是出於個人恩怨
He was hands off. All of hiss were impersonal.
可釋放才兩天 就殺了Stacy Ryan 綁架自己的女兒
2 days after hs released, he kills stacy ryan and he kidnaps his dauter.
這完全是針對個人 也很情緒化
It's both personal and emotional.
他對犯案並無情感投入 所以往往成功 但一旦投入感情
But the minute he's invested,
比如和女兒在一起時 他就放鬆了警惕 導致被抓 這也可以理解
like with his daughter, he lethis guard down and gets caught. It makes sense.
看來不像我們所想的那麼難搞
So he's not the hard-ass we thought he was.
但如果他只是想得到Jenny 不已經得到了嘛 完全可以離開
But if jenny were what he wanted, he had her. He could have left.
沒錯 我們以為他會帶著她去加拿大 對吧?
Yeah,we thought he took her and ran to canada,right?
這麼說來很合理啊 為什麼沒這麼做呢?
That theory made sense. Why didn't he?
- 事故現場採集的照片 - Emily現在怎麼樣?
- Pictures from the accident. - Any word on emily?
- 目前正和醫生吵著呢 - 那就還好
- Apparently she's arguing with the doctors. - That's good.
這一定是頗費周折才辦到的
This took a lot to pull off.
如果他背後有一堆人可以召集呢?
What if he's got a group of guys to call on?
我也這麼覺得 雖說所有的銀行劫案都是個人所為
I agree.All those bank jobs were a solo,
但看上去 一個人很難策劃得這麼周全
but this is a lot for one man to orchestrate.
知道他為什麼殺害Stacy Ryan了麼?
Figured out why he killed stacy ryan?
還沒找到她和Schrader有任何關聯 但也許和他的同夥有關係
We haven't found any connection to schrader, but he may be connected to the partner.
怎麼說?
How?
殺了她 很可能是把他救出來的一個條件
Killing her might have been advance payment for breaking him out of custody.
- 在 - Garcia 需要所有Stacy Ryan的信息
- Yes. - Garcia,i need evething you've got on stacy ryan.
你說他逃了是什麼意思?
What do you mean he got away?
- 有人把他救了出去 - 噢 天啊
- Somebody broke him out of custody. - Oh,god.
你們倆必須待在這
We're gonna keep the two of you here.
會有警官隨時在此監視所有情況
There's gonna be an officer standing watch the entire ti.
你們都找不到他 這保證我們的安全 啥時是個頭啊
You can't find him, how long will you keep us safe.
- 夫人 我們會找到他的 - 你不瞭解Dale
- ma'am,we will find him. - You don't know dale.
他想要什麼 就一定會得到
When he wants something, he gets it.
你能想到有誰可能幫他的嗎?
- 他從來不相信任何人 - 這不是信不信任的問題
- Heoesn't trust anybody. - It's not necessarily about trust.
可能是他曾經有恩於某人 那個人不過是來回報而已?
Maybe somebody who's indebted to him and he was trying to colle on it?
我真的不知道
I don't know.
Jenny
Jenny.
一直都只有你和你爸爸嗎?
You and your dadere alone the entire time?
卡車和小木屋堻ㄗS人?
Nobody was in the truck or the cabin?
- 沒人 - 誰會幫Dale幹這事?
- Nobody. - Who uld do this for dale?
誰會奮不顧身地幫他?
Who would risk everything to help him?
那就是我們要找的
At's what we nd to find out.
Stacy Ryan的人生只有兩種狀態 吸毒 和等著吸毒
Acy ryan had two times in her life-- when she was high and when she was waiting to get high.
我發現他倆之間的唯一聯繫 就是她哥哥在五年前...
The only thread I have between them is that her brother spent time with schrader upstate like...
和Schrader一起待過一段
5 years ago.
- 為什麼Schrader要殺一個癮君子? - 這沒道理啊
- Why would schrader kill a junkie? - It doesn't make sense.
- 哥哥現在在哪? - 死了
- Where's the brother now? - Dead.
並不感覺Schrader是在胡亂犯案
It doesn't feel like schrader does anything randomly.
Stacy對他來說 肯定有什麼特別的地方
Stacy must have meant something to him.
是的  但...到底是什麼?
Yeah,but... What?
不用麻煩了 我看見她了
Never mind,i see her.
我來接她離開 謝謝
I can take her from here. Thanks.
- 謝謝 我能走了 - 坐著
- Thank you. I can walk. - Sit.
我就喜歡推著你走
I like pushing you around.
還疼麼?
Does it hurt?
如果你指的是我整個身子 那就是了
If by "it" you mean my entire body,then yes.
Jenny看見什麼了嗎?
Did jenny see anything?
- 她從沒看見同夥 - 太糟了
- Shnever saw the partner. - Oh,what the hell?
他們在事故現場不遠處 發現了一輛廢棄卡車
They found a truck ditched a few miles from the accident.
牌照沒了 但肯定是撞著你們的那輛
Plates were missing, but the front end definitely hit your car.
所以同夥在樹林堿搢ㄓF全過程 逃跑了 還去偷了一輛卡車?
Ok,so the partner saw everything in the woods, he ran away and stole a truck?
他到底是何方神聖?
Who is this guy?
他知道你們會走那條道回局
He knew you were taking that road back to the station.
他埋伏在那 然後伏擊你們 這整件事也太滴水不漏了
He waited for you and he crashed into you. This whole thing feels meticulous.
所以他需要同夥來佈置其它的事
Ok,so he needs the partner for something else.
為了什麼?
For what,though?
不清楚 可他從始至終一直被鎖住的
Well,i don't know. I mean,he was locked up all this time.
他盤算了一整天 應該還有很多備用計劃
He planned the whole day. He should have had backup plans for his backup plans.
他的前妻有幾個小時不在家
His ex shouldn't have been home for a few hours,
在我們出現之前 他有足夠的時間和Jenny越過邊界
So he clearly had enough time to get across the border with jenny until we showed up.
但是他選擇留在當地 藏身於小屋中
But he stayed local, holed up in that cabin.
已經得到想要的了 他應該立刻就逃跑
He had what he wanted. He could have just run.
肯定還有其它什麼事 讓他留在了洛克波特
There's gotta be something else keeping him in lockport.
我看著他勒死Bunting 卻無能為力
I couldn't stop him from choking bunting.
- Emily 不要這樣 - 就眼睜睜地看著
- Emily,don't do that. - He was right there.
新聞上鋪天蓋地都是Schrader的照片
Schrader's face is all over the news.
他已經逃了兩個小時了 還是毫無頭緒
He's been on the run foalmost 2 hours and 're no closer to catching him.
我們需要找到他的同夥
We need to find the partner.
- 怎麼樣了? - 感覺像是被卡車撞了
- How are you? - I feel like I got hit by a truck.
- 這塈 - 謝謝
- Here,sit. - Thanks.
Garcia 告訴大家你剛剛說給我的
Uh,garcia,tell everyone what you just told me.
我挖掘出了更多Schrader的過去
I have unearthed more of schrader's past.
我們已經知道 他在90年代搶劫了紐約州的15家銀行
Now,what we do know is that he robbed 15 banks inhe state of new york in the nineties.
但是 魅力驚人聰明無比的我剛剛發現
However,what your resident glamour-puss smarty-pants just found out
大部分的贓款還沒有被追回
Was that most of that money was never recovered.
- 那在哪呢? - 我猜最大的可能 是只有他知道
- Where is it? - My best guess-- only he knows.
待在洛克波特的好理由
Good reason to stick around lockport.
最後一次搶劫 被捕的那次 應該也只是按著例行計劃吧?
The last robbery, the one that put him away, should have been routine, right?
- 怎麼就被抓了呢? - 也許什麼人出賣了他
- So what happened? - Maybe someone turned him in.
他一直自己行動 誰出賣了他?
He kept to himself, always worked alone. Who'd turn him in?
我們遺漏了什麼人
We're missing somebody.
- Garcia - 好的 這就查 長官
- Rcia. - Yes,checking,sir.
- 這是為了什麼? - 明天早上之前什麼都不用做
- What's this all about? - Nothing to do till morning.
你有什麼困擾?
What's your problem?
猶豫是成功的絆腳石
Hesitation puts obstacle in the path.
無畏能使我們不再猶豫 無畏能驅走恐懼
Boldness eliminates them. Boldness strikes fear.
恐懼造就權力
Fear creates authority.
"權力的48條定律" 聽說過沒?
"the 48 laws of power." You know It?
想要對我開槍嗎?
you want to shoot me?
我說謝謝了沒?
Have I said thanks yet?
好了 Schrader的逮捕記錄引出了 另一個叫Dan Otey的銀行搶劫犯
Ok. Records leading up to schrader's arrest show this other bank robber named dan otey.
他有足夠的時間
And he was looking at copious amounts of time,
他簽了個協議 突然間Schrader就被逮捕了
Then he strikes a deal and all of a sudden schrader is arrested.
不可能是巧合
It can't be a coincidence.
罪犯之間互相收買 倒不少見
You know,it's not uncommon for criminals to buy jobs off one another.
也許Schrader這麼做了 Dan Otey出賣了他 得到了減刑
Maybe that's what schrader did, budan otey sold him out for a lesser sentence.
難以理解 Otey背叛了他 現在卻成了同夥?
It doesn't make sense. Otey was a rat and now he's the partner?
說對了 Schrader不會信任他 如果可能的話 他會希望他死掉
Yeah,you're right. Schrader wouldn't trust him. If anything, he'd want him dead.
有可能 但也會先利用他
Probably, but he'd use him fir.
他告訴Otey他欠他一命 而這件事可以讓他撿回條命
He'd telotey that he owes him one and that he might save his life
要他能幫助自己躲過這次追捕
if he helps him get out of this m.
他現在在哪 Garcia?
Where's he now,garcia?
Dan Otey是當地人 住在7號公路
Uh,dan otey is a local. He lives off of route 7.
沒有人 我們上
Nobody's here.Let's go.
- 你爸爸在家嗎? - 你是誰?
- is your ddy home? - Who are you?
關上門!
Close the door!
別這麼做
冷靜 我只是嚇一嚇他
Ca down. I'm just gonna scare him a little bit.
嘿 Dan!
Hey,dan!
你讓你的兒子應門?
You sent your son to the door?
懦夫
Coward.
- 他的妻子和兒子都在家 - 他們沒事嗎?
- His wife and son were home. - Are they ok?
他的搭檔帶他們去了樓上 Schrader毀了現場
While schrad destroyed the place.
Emily正陪著妻子
Emily is with the wife right now.
Dan已經改過自新了
Dan had tued everything around.
他變好了 生活也終於好轉了
He was clean, life was finally good.
但是我總是不敢相信 你知道嗎?
But I was always afraid to believe I you know?
因為他可能被殺掉
Because then he could be taken ay.
請節哀
I'm so sorry.
另一個人 他什麼長相?
The other man-- what did he look like?
白人...40多歲...短髮
Uh,white... Mid-40s... Short hair...
我記不清了
I don't know.
你以前見過他嗎?
Had you ever seen him before?
見過Dale 但是沒見過另外一個
Dale,yeah. The other guy,no.
我們正在查 Schrader怎麼認識他的同夥的
We're trying to figure out how schrader knows his partner.
我不知道
I have no idea.
他們互相說什麼了?
How did they talk to each other?
啥也沒說
They didn't.
Dale把房子砸了 另一個把我們帶到樓上
Dale trashed the place, and the other guy took us upstairs.
他一直推著我...
He kept pushing and...
Jason.... 我不知道會發生什麼
Jason.... I didn't know what was gonna happen.
他傷你了嗎?
Did he hurt you?
他只是嚇我們 把我們鎖在堶悸漫迠
He just scared us. He locked us in the back room.
他把你們鎖進屋子 就沒有了?
He locked you in the room and that's it?
是 他叫我們閉嘴 並且一直扣著門
Yeah. He told us to shut up and keep it locked.
但是Jason一直哭個不停
But jason wouldn't stop crying.
這可不是我們說好的
This wasn't the deal.
- 是嗎? - 我可沒有同意要殺人
- Really? - I didn't sign up to kill anybody.
你救了我 你把我從車里拉了出來 記得嗎?
You saved my ass. You pulled me out of that car,remember?
- 然後才有人死了 - 我做不來
- Then people died. - I can't do it. I won't.
不 你會的
Yes,you will.
你恐嚇了那家人 殺了父親
You terrorized that family. You killed their father.
不用擔心 孩子還小 他不會記得父親的
Don't worry. The kid is young. He won't remember him.
我也殺了警察 可別忘了他
I also killed that cop. Don't forget about him.
- 你很享受 - 對 我是
- You enjoyed it. - Yes,i did.
但是你沒有阻止我
And you didn't stop me.
明白了 你做你想做的事
I get it. You gotta do what you gotta do.
我做我的 來吧 快要結束了
And I want what I want. Come on,bro. Almost done.
Schrader掌控著一切
Schrader gets off on power.
這和錢一樣成為他的動機
That and money are what motivate him.
還有復仇 11年後 他變成了殺人犯
And revenge. 11 years away, he comes out a murderer.
同夥應該和他一樣膽大
Who needs a partner, somebody as bold as him.
他們在哪媢J見的?
And where'd they meet?
Schrader遠遠的 一直忍耐著
Schrader was away and patient.
一出來就先和他的同夥接上了頭
The minute he got out, he hooked up with his partner first,
然後在綁架自己女兒的路上 殺了Stacy Ryan
And then he killed stacy ryan on his way to kidnap his daughter.
- 那一天堣痐F什麼? - 錢
- What's missing from his day. - The money.
帶走女兒卻留下錢 這講不通
He took his daughter but left the money. That doesn't make any sense.
他有其它的計劃 保證在加拿大的生存嗎?
Did he have another plan how to support himself in canada?
他只知道犯罪的生活 不可能改變 時間的流逝已經證明了這點
He's only known a life of crime. He's incapable of change. Time away proved that.
Otey的老婆說 同夥把他們鎖起來 好像他不想傷害他們
Well,otey's wife said that the partner locked them away, like he didn't want them to get hurt.
他想要保護 很奇怪 對吧?
He was protective. T?
他們都是支配型人格 卻像是一個扮紅臉 一個扮黑臉
They're both dominant personalities, but they sound like they played good cop/bad cop.
距離案件發生已經4個小時了
Well,it's been 4 hours since the accident.
你還覺得我沒緩過來?
You still think I'm in shock?
只有一種辦法證明了
There's one way to find out.
第一件事 我們到局堮釣噾_匙
Ok. First thing, we go to the staon, gonna get the key.
然後我們去9點開門的那家銀行 就大功告成了
Then we go to the bank which opens at 9:00. Then we're done.
沒那麼容易 我說過的
It's not that easy. I told you.
對我來說不容易 但你 每個人都喜歡你
Not for me. But you-- Everybody loves you.
好吧 我加入 然後呢
Ok,i do this. Then what?
- 然後就結束了 - 不
- Then it's over. - No.
- 不? - 不 我不可能還能活著
- No? - No. There's no version of me surviving this.
你得到你想要的 我就活不成了
You get what you want, I'm dead.
如果你這麼想的話 就來吧
Well,if you believe that, do it.
來吧  你現在就能阻止一切
Go ahead. You can stop this right now.
你想要我死 有多想? 下手啊
You want me dead. How bad? Come on.
殺了我啊 怎麼了?
Kill me. What?
還要我幫你嗎? 要嗎?
You need my help? Is that what you need?
你知道我的 不達到目的我絕不罷休
You know I'm not gonna stop this unl I get what I want.
我不會停手的 但你可以
I'm not gonna stop it, but you can.
想阻止這一切嗎? 那就動手吧 結束這一切
You want to d it? Then do it. End it.
來啊 動手啊 把握機會 你就如願了
Come on. Do it. Take a chance that this all works out for you.
來啊! 來啊! 動手啊! 來啊! 動手啊! 結束這一切! 動手啊! 來啊!
Comen! Come on! Do it! Come on! Comen! End it! Do it! Come on!
就知道你下不了手
that's what I thought.
你做不出這種事 Joe 從來都下不了手
It's not in you,joe. never was.
好 深呼吸 Prentiss
All right, take a deep breath,prentiss.
- 我準備好了 - 好的
- Let's justo this. - All right.
告訴我你看見了什麼 當時天黑嗎?
Tell me what you saw was it dark?
黑啊 你也在 你知道的
Yeah. You were there. You kn it was.
- 認真點 - 好的
- Come on,now. - Ok.
車子埵酗偵簳道?
What did it smell like inside the car?
- 濕濕的 - 那你很熱咯?
- Sweat. - So you were hot?
對 我就-- 開了點窗
Ye. I--i opened the window a little bit.
很安靜啊
It's really quiet.
當時路上還有別的車子嗎?
Are there any other cars on the road?
- 有一輛車在過來 - 是什麼顏色的?
- There's one coming. - What color is it?
我... 燈太亮了
I... It's too bright.
好 但你還是看了 你看到了
Ok,but you looked at it. You saw it.
是輛四門轎車 是黑色的
It's a 4-door hybrid, black.
Schrader呢?
Where was schrader?
- 他在看窗外 - 看起來在等誰嗎?
- He's looking out the window. - Was he waiting for something?
- 然後又來了一輛車 - 轎車還是卡車?
- Here comes another car. - A car or the truck?
是那輛卡車 Schrader看著它
It's the truck. Schrader sees it.
然後就不對勁了 他... 解開了安全帶
That's when it happens. He's... Out of his seatbelt.
彎下了腰
He's hunched over.
然後他解開了前面的手銬
And he gets his cuffs out in front of him.
好 然後呢?
Ok,then what?
呃 Bunting把車停在路邊然後-- 然後 Schrader又扣好了安全帶
Uh,bunting pulled over, and--and schrader put his seatbelt back on.
他知道馬上就要出事了
He knew it was coming.
卡車是從哪個方向來的?
Where did the truck come from?
呃 我們後面 呃 不是-- 是前面來的
Uh,behind us. Uh,no-- It was in front of us.
誰在開車 Prentiss?
Who was driving,prentiss?
- 我不知道 我看不見 - 好 沒關係 沒關係
- I don't know. I can't see. - Ok. It's all right, it's all right.
- 你確定是卡車? - 確定 是輛很大的卡車
- You're sure it was the truck? - Yeah. It's a big truck.
再想想 誰在開車? 誰在開車?
Think. Who was driving? Who was driving?
白人男性 40歲左右
A white male,40s.
好了 接著你們的車停了下來
All right,now your car stoprolling.
對 我動不了
Yeah. I'm pinned.
安全帶卡住了
My seatbelt is jammed.
我透不過氣了 什麼都看不見 能聽見--
I can't breathe. I can't see anything.I can hear--
哦 天吶 他在勒Bunting的脖子
oh,god, he's killing bunting.
- 但他的同伴還沒出現? - 沒有
- But the partner's not the yet? - No.
他在哪?
Where is he?
正在跑過來
He's running towards us.
- 他穿什麼衣服? - 牛仔褲和靴子
- What's he wearing? - Jeans. Boots.
你搞什麼? 幹嘛殺條子?
What's wrong with you? You killed a cop?
Bunting死了他很慌張
He's freaked out that bunting's dead.
- 他為什麼這麼在意? - 我不知道
- Why would he care? - I don't know.
但是他不讓他殺我
But he won't let him kill me.
- 把槍給我 - 她是FBI
- Give me the gun. - She's a fed.
她知道我們倆了現在
She knows that there's two of us now.
他一直在和他說...
And he keeps telling him to...
- 壓著點 - 壓在出血的地方
- Put pressure on it. - On the bleeding.
- 會沒事的 - 好嗎
- It's gonna be ok. - Ok.
等等 他是在和我說話
Wait. He was talking to me.
用力壓著
There's a lot ot pressure on it.
你會沒事的 聽見了嗎?
You're gonna be all right. Understand?
他知道我們會走那條路
He knew we were on that road.
Bunting死了他很難過
He was upset that bunting was dead.
他不讓Schrader殺了我
He wouldn't let schrader kill me.
他一直叫我壓著傷口
He kept telling me to put pressure on it.
他還很鎮定 好像以前就這麼幹過
And he was calm,like he's
他是在幫我
He was helping me.
他把Dan Otey的家人帶到樓上 不讓Schrader傷害他們
He took dan otey's family upstairs, protected them from schrader.
你們真以為會有個好人和 Dale Schrader一樣的罪犯搭檔嗎?
Do we really think a good guy hooked up with a criminal like dale schrader?
您有一通留言
You have one saved message.
Joe 親愛的 是我
joe,honey,it's me.
他找到我們了 我們三個 我也不知道我們現在在哪
Ey got us. All of us. I don't know where we are.
- 天啊 我對不起你 - 救我 爸爸!
- God,i am so sorry. - Helus,daddy!
照他說的做好嗎? 求你 他讓你做什麼就做什麼
just do what he says,ok? Please just do whatever he says.
Joe 救救我們
Joe,help us.
Joe 親愛的 是我 他找到我們了
Joe,honey,it's me. He got us.
你就要做到了 幹得真棒
You've almost got it. You're doing so good.
對不起 求求你了
I'm sorry. Lease.
哦 我的天啊 我的天 求求你不要!
Oh,my god. My god,please stop!
別碰他!
Don't you touch him!
不是他的錯 是我讓他解的
It's not his fault. I told him to do it.
- 不 等等! 你要幹什麼? - 媽媽! 媽媽!
- No,wait! What are you doing? - Mom! Mommy!
不要! 別帶走我的孩子!
No! Don't take my kid!
媽媽! 媽媽! 媽媽 救我!
Mom! Mommy! Mom,help!
媽媽!
Mom!
那Schrader是怎麼讓他入伙的?
So how did schrader get this guy to sign on?
好人幹壞事
Good people do bad things.
要我說 常有的事
I'm just saying, it happens.
是沒錯 可這個同夥不想讓我死
Right. But this partner wouldn't let me die.
他還保護了Otey的家人
He protected otey's family.
就在同一天 他卻協助一個重罪犯潛逃
In the same day, he helped a convicteder felon escape custody.
他也太忠心了
His loyalties are all over the place.
這人聽起來無路可走了 也許他需要錢
The guy sounds desperate. Maybe he needs some money.
Schrader可還留著一大筆錢呢
I mean,schrader's got a lot of it still out there.
可能答應給他一份
He could have promised him a cut.
啊 我不這麼想 他可是三起謀殺案 一起綁架案的幫兇啊
Ah,i don't know. He's an accomplice to 3 murders and a kidnapping.
你會為了錢幹這些嗎?
Is there enough mone out there
那就是比錢重要的東西
so it's something bigger than the money.
嗯 也許是Schrader威脅他的
Um,maybe schrader's threatening him.
- 把柄? - 一定是很重要的把柄
- Leverage? - It would have to be big.
我們能抓到Schrader是因為 他綁架了自己的女兒
We caught schrader because he kidnapped his daughter.
他很情緒化 戒備鬆懈
He was emotionaland his guard w.
很明顯 家人對他的重要性 超過了我們的預期
Clearly,family means more to him than we thought.
Schrader的前妻曾強迫他 放棄對Jenny的監護權
Schrader's ex-wife he was eforced him to give up Custody jenny.
或許他也想讓這人嘗嘗 失去家人的滋味
Maybe he wants this guy to know what it feels like to lose s family,too.
- 我覺得就是報復 - 或許就是
- It sounds like revenge to me. - Maybe it is.
知道我不能理解什麼嗎?
You know what I just don't get?
為什麼大家總覺得你是個英雄
Why pele think you're a hero.
我瞭解他們不瞭解的那一面 其實你只想成為和我一樣的人
I know something they don't. You want to be just like me.
老實巴交的無聊人 太容易被看穿了
Honest men bore you. They're too predictable.
要你平凡生活還不如要你去死 那你就冒點險 試探底限
And you'd rather die than be ordinary, so you take ris and you push the limits.
可你從小就被教導要做個好人
But you were raised to be a good guy.
你骨子奡N這樣 不能控制
It's in your blood. You can't help it.
可那樣就泯滅了一小部分的你
But that kills you a little bit.
所以你要想辦法從好人變成壞人
That's why you had to figure out a way for a good guy you to be bad,
所以你就遇到了我
And that's how you got into my world.
- 我猜得對不對? - 我想和他們說話
- Am I close? - I want to talk to them.
你聽到留言了 也看到照片了
You got your message and that picture.
我怎麼知道你是不是早就把他們殺了?
How do I know you haven't killed them already?
你只能相信我
You have to trust me.
我太失望了
Well,i'm disappointed.
可你老婆孩子會受不了的 因為他們不一定非得死
But your wife and your kids are gonna be devastated 'cause they didn't have to die.
反正你也會殺了我 傷害他們有什麼意義
Look,you're gonna kill me. There's no point in hurting them.
你算什麼父親?
What kind of father are you?
我們已經說好了 只有我知道他們在哪
We've been over this. I'm the only one who ows where they are.
只要我還活著 他們就沒事
As long as I'm alive, they're safe.
如果你不幫我了 他們就會死 怎麼樣?
If you stop helping me, they're dead. How's that?
Scader的案子有進展了嗎?
Anything on scader's case?
很普通的嫌疑人-- 法官 律師
The usual suspects-- judge,lawyers.
今天早上都通知他們了
They're all accounted for this morning.
如果這是報復 一定有什麼人很排斥他
If it's revenge, then it's gotta be someone who put him away.
他不是警察逮捕的 也不是法官判的刑
Well,it's not the officers who arrested him or the judge who sentenced him.
到底是誰?
Then who is it?
Garcia 把執法部門每個參與了 Schrader案子的探員名字給我
Garcia,i need the names of every law enforcement agent involved in the schrader case.
你都知道了啊
Yoknow everybody.
是的 還要他被捕那年所有員工的資料
Yeah,but I want every single empyee the year that he was arrested.
好 一分鐘
Ok,give me a minute.
要一分鐘? 加油 寶貝 不會掉線了吧?
A whole minute? Come on,baby girl,what, are you losing your touch?
哦 給我講話當心點
Oh,watch your pretty mouth.
人事材料來了
Personnel records come at you now.
- 還有誰在職? - 大多數人都還在
- Who's still active? - Most.
他會利用一個在職警官嗎?
Would he risk using an activofficer?
看他有多恨他們了 有人退休了嗎?
Depends on how much he hates them. Has anyone retired?
有 兩個 看看-- Matt Massey 和Jeff Messick
Yeah,two of them. Let's see--matt massey, jeff messick.
- 都結婚有孩子了 白人 50幾歲 - 等等 能給我看看照片嗎?
- Both married with kids, white,in eir 50s. - Wait,can I see those pictures?
不是
No.
他為什麼就不去找逮捕他的警察呢?
Why wouldn't he go after one of the officers who arrested him?
這樣才最說得通是報復啊
It makes the most sense for revenge.
嘿嘿 等等 夥計們 看這個
Hey,wait a minute,guys. Listen to this.
有一目擊證人沒有代表Schrader作證
There was a witness who never testified on schrader's behalf.
Schrader會認為這是背叛
Schrader could see that as a betrayal.
他一出獄就利用他作案
He getout of prison and uses him to get what he wants.
Garcia 查一下Schrader案子的一個 目擊證人的檔案 Joey Short
Garcia,i want you to run a history on a witness from the schrader case, joey short.
Joey Short 66年出生在紐約
Joey short. Was born in '66 in nyc.
除了混吸毒聚會 沒幹過別的正經活
Didn't hold a lot of jobs except for construction.
- 是戒毒中心的常客 - 他現在住哪?
- In and out of rehab. - Where is he now?
他最新的顯示住址是10年前的
His last known address wa10 years ago.
- 他在坐牢嗎? - 沒有
- Did he do time? - No.
再查查 Gacia 人不會無緣無故失蹤的
Come on,gcia. People don't just disappear.
這人的檔案有很多漏洞
This guy's got a history with a lot of holes in it.
他去過戒毒中心 也許會遵守諾言
He went to rehab. You know,maybe this guy had to walk the walk.
- 他是臥底 - 這樣就說得通了
- He was undercover. - That makes sense.
這些人什麼都幹得出來 能冒險 不管是工作上還是私生活方面
Those guys e up for anything, and they take big risks, professionally and personally.
他的行為也能解釋了 好人幹壞事
It explains his behavior,too. Good guy doing bad things.
Garcia Joey Short的真名是什麼?
Garcia,can you get us joey short's real name?
我這兒沒有
It's not here.
如果Schrader能找到 我們也能找到
Well,if schrader can find it,so can we.
這人得是Schrer的朋友 那他們應該是同年
The guy needed to be schrer's friend, so they're probably around the same age.
查一下90年代早期的學院畢業生名單
Look forcademy graduates in the early nineties.
好的
Ok.
有沒有什麼人沒有進警察局工作?
Did any of them not go into police work?
寶貝 我聽不懂了
Baby,i don't follow you.
如果他是臥底 就要斷絕 和學院有關的任何聯繫
If he we undercover, then anything tied to the academy would have to be severed.
這人畢了業 就要馬上 以Joey Short的身份開始工作
I mean,the guy graduated, be he had to immediately start working his history as joey short.
他混進吸毒聚會 和銀行劫犯取得聯繫
He went into cstruction, made his contacts in the bank robbery world,
然後他認識了Schrader 贏得他的信任
And then he met schrader, earned schrader's trust,
把他送進監獄以後就全身而退
And then turned him in and got out of the game.
好了 有幾個人中途退出了
Ok. Here's a couple of guys look like theyropped out.
有照片嗎?
You got any pictures?
這就發給你
Sending them your way now.
就是這個人 照片上老了十歲 不過就是他
That is thguy. That picture is 10 years old, but at's him.
他是Joe Muller 有個老婆 兩個孩子
That is joe mulr. He has a wife and 2 kids.
絕對就是這個人 他現在在哪?
That's definitely the guy. Where is he now?
- Betts - 在?
- Betts. - Yes?
Joe Muller 讓我好好看看你
Joe muller. Let me look at you.
- 最近怎麼樣? - 有點忙
- How's life? - It's a ride.
- Molly和孩子們呢? - 很好 他們都很好
- Molly,the kids? - Good. They're good.
- 你來這幹嘛? - 呃 你知道的 辦案子
- What are you doing he? - Just,uh,you know,work
- 呃 他們是不是開除你了? - 是的 夫人
- Uh,they stopped paying you,didn't they?
別跟我"夫人""夫人"地瞎客氣 你有什麼需要?
Don't you ma'am me. What do you need?
- 嗯...5分鐘就好? - 沒問題
- Just,uh,5 minutes? - You got it.
你最好了
You're the best.
好的謝了 Muller不在家 家堥S人
Ok,thanks. Muller's not at home. No one is.
他妻子沒去上班 孩子昨天和今天都沒去學校
His wife didn't show up at work, the kids weren't at school yesterday or today.
Schrader很可能抓了他們當人質
Schrer probably has them hostage.
- 是啊 但在哪呢? - Joe Muller能為他做什麼呢?
- Yeah,but whe? - What could joe muller for him?
他能幫他拿到的東西 就只有錢了
The only thing that's left. He can get him the moy.
- 好吧 根本就沒人知道它在哪 - Schrader知道
- Well,no one even knows where it is. - Schrader knows.
這些傢伙把錢藏在哪呢?
Where do these guys hide money?
某個安全的地方
Someplace safe.
他會膽子那麼大敢把 錢藏到保管箱媔?
Would he be bold enough to hide it a safe deposit box?
大盜把錢存銀行? 是啊 也許吧
A thief using a bank? Yeah,maybe.
Schrader不能進銀行 到處都有通緝他的圖像
Schrader can't walk into a bank. His face is everywhere.
要是Muller走進去 是沒有人會在意的
No one would think twice if muller walked in.
他必須得有鑰匙
He'd have to have a key.
Schrader一案的物證都在哪?
Where's the physical evidence from the schrader case?
不在我們手堣F
We don't have it.
好吧 如果我們可以想出Schrader把 錢藏在哪 我們就會知道他要去哪堣F
Well,if we can figure out where schrader hid the money, we'll know where he's going.
謝謝你  我們是FBI的
Thank you. We're with the fbi.
我們正在辦Dale Schrader案
We're working e dale schrader case.
- Joe Muller是在幫你們嗎? - 沒
- Is joe muller helping you? - No.
- 他剛還在這 - 什麼時候?
- He was just here. - When?
- 2分鐘前 - 謝謝你
- 2 minutes ago. - Thank you.
我家人在哪?
Where's my family?
希爾克雷斯特大道2839號
2839 hillcrest drive.
希爾克雷斯特? 你把他們放在城?
Hillcrt? You got them downtown?
不 我的錢在那
No,that's where my money is.
然後呢? 這就永遠不會結束對吧?
Then what? This is never gonna end,is it?
把車停下! 雙手放在 我能看見的地方!
Stop the car! Put your hands where I can see them!
- 別開槍 - Schrader把它放下!
- Don't shoot. - Schrader,put it down!
把它放下!
Put it down!
你真的會讓我把他的腦袋打開花?
You really gonna let me bl his brains out?
- 放下 不然我開槍了! - 有什麼問題嗎 探員?
- Drop it or i'll shoot! - What's wrong,agent?
你還在為我殺掉你的夥計難過嗎?
You still upset that I killed your buddy?
他也跟這人一樣有孩子嗎?
Did he have kids like this one?
- 看看他 她已經氣壞了 - 別殺他
- Ook at her. She's pissed. - Don't kill him.
看啊 看看她眼睛堛獐垂
Look athat look in her eyes.
她有那個決心了 她會開槍的
She's nna. She is gonna do it.
來吧 你要怎麼辦?
Come on, what are y gonna do?
- 別開槍 - 別那麼干Schrader
- Don't shoot. - Don't do it,schrader.
你胳膊怎麼樣了?
How's your arm?
嘿 不! 不! 他們在哪? 我家人在哪?
Hey, no! No! Where are they? Where's my family?
- 告訴我他們在哪! - 退後! 讓開!
- Tell me where they are! - Back up! Get away!
- 救他! - 讓開!退後!
她剛害死了我的家人
She just killed my family.
- 你剛害死了我的家人! - 冷靜!
- You just killed my family! - Calm down!
你剛害死了我的家人!
You killed my family!
停!
Stop!
唯一知道我家人在哪的人 現在死了
The only person who knew where my family was and now he's dead.
我一直都有機會殺掉他
I had every chance to kill him.
但我不能 因為他手埵釦畬a人
But I couldn't. Because he had my family.
兩天了 在某個地方
2 days. Somewhere.
而這張照片是 他們還活著的唯一證明?
And this photograph is the only proof of life?
我的手機呢?
Where's my phone?
Joe親愛的 是我
Joe,honey,it's me.
他抓了我們 我們所有人 我不知道我們在哪
He got us. All of us. I don't know where we are.
- 上帝 我太抱歉了 - 救救我們 爸爸!
- God,i am so sorry. - Help us,daddy!
就按他說的做 好嗎? 不管他說什麼就照做吧 求你了
Just do what he says,ok?
我會讓Garcia追蹤這個的
I'm gonna get gaia to trace this.
- 未知的名字和號碼 - 她可能會能幫上忙
- Unknown name, unknown nuer. - She might be able to help.
只有一通電話?
There was only one phoneall?
我試圖叫他 讓我再跟她們說一次話 但他不肯
Tried to get him to let me talk to them again,but hwouldn't.
那堣@定沒人看著她們
There must not be yone there watching them.
這麼說 他把一家人藏在一個 沒人能聽見她們呼救的地方
So he hid a family where no one hrs them call for help.
某個偏僻的地方 那個小屋?
Someplace remote. Thatabin?
不 當地警察都快把那給拆了 那堥S有人了
No. The locals tore it apart. There's no onehere.
他們在哪呢?
Where are they?
自從他抓了你的家人後 你一直看著Schrader
You saw schrader since he's had youfamily.
你看見或聽到了某些事情 這堶惜@定有些線索的
You saw something or heard it. There's got be some clue.
你最後一次見到你家人是什麼時候?
When was the st time you w your family?
等一下Joe 我得去拿上我的手機
Hold on,joe,i've got to get my phon.
哦 嗯...它就在這
oh,uh,it's rht here.
- 哦 都快沒電了 - 我知道  抱歉
- Co drains the battery. - I know. Sorry.
好的 晚點再見Muller夫人
Ok. See you later, mrs. Muller.
- 看你運氣好不好咯 - 你注意到街上什麼車了嗎?
- If you're lucky. - You notice any cars on the street?
什麼也沒
Nothing.
讓我幫你把安全帶扣好
Let me get your seatbelt in.
我們的日程每天都是一樣的
Our routine's the same every day.
孩子們8:15必須到校 然後Molly去上班
The kids have to be at school by 8:15, then molly heads to work.
她昨天和今天都沒能上班 她的路線是?
She didn't make it to either yesterday. What was her route?
嗯...沿7號公路向北 再向東上22號公路
Uh,north on route 7, east on 22.
- 那路線在早間時段是孤立的嗎? - 不
- Is that route isolated during the morning commute? - No.
如果他在監視 有很大可能 她根本沒能把車開出車道
If he was watching, there's a good chance she never left the driveway.
我先開車走了
I drove out first.
開車
Drive.
我就把她們丟在了那
I just left them there.
他在哪找到你的?
Where did he find you?
在五金商店
At the hardware store.
我知道你是誰
I know who you are.
他告訴我 這11年間他試圖 搞清楚他是如何被關起來的
He told me how for 11 years he'd been trying to figure out how he got locked up.
他知道Otey出賣了他搶劫的事 但那還不足以把他關那麼久
He knew otey had ratted him out for the robbery, but that wasn't enough to put him away.
他說 搞不清楚的一點 就在我身上
He said I was the piece that didn't fit.
- 他明白了我是個警察 - 然後他綁架了你的家人
- He figured out I was a cop. - And he took your family.
- 你見過這名女子嗎? - 是的 我以為就是個吸毒的
- Did you ever see this woman? - Yeah. I think she's some junkie.
我見到了她 這時他剛和我說完...
I saw her right after he told me...
你幫我 你家人就活命 你不幫 他們就會死
You help me, your family lives. You don't,they die.
停車 就在這
Pull overright . Right here.
Stacy 我沒時間管這些
Stacy. I don't have time for this.
我告訴過你 等這事結束了 會有更多的
I told you,there'll be more when it's over.
我找了幾個人幫忙 而他們不想等
I got some people helping and they don't want to wait.
那不是我的問題
That's not my problem.
我哥說你就是個狗娘養的
My brother said you were a son of a bitch.
你知道他在幹什麼嗎? 你知道這堶惘酗偵繲?
You know what he's dng? You know what's in here?
- 怎麼了? - 閉嘴 閉嘴
- Shut up.Shut up.
她是誰?
Who is she?
走 快點 開車 走!
Go. Come on. Drive. Go!
- 你不知道她說的是什麼? - 不
- You didn't know what she was talking about? - No.
停下
Pull over.
怎麼處理她?
What are you gonna do with her?
- 他本可以把屍體留在那小巷堛 - 為什麼沒有?
- He could have left the body in the alley. - Why didn'te?
他不想有人注意到那地方
He didn't want to draw attention to that place.
- 那是哪? - 嗯...Van Wyck南邊
- Where was it? - Uh,south of van wyck.
- 地方不太好? - 廢棄的地兒 被癮君子們當了據點
- Bad area? - Abandoned. Junkies took over.
扣留人質的好地方
Perfect place to leave hostages.
你能帶我們回到那堨h嗎?
Can you take us back there?
等等 你認為她知道我家人的事
Wait. You think she knew about my family.
她被殺 是唯一不符合側寫的事件 而現在就能解釋了
Her muer was the only thing that didn't fit, and now it makes sse.
Schrader殺了她封口
Schrader killed her to shut her up.
Rossi 轉過去 轉過去!FBI!
Rossi. Turn around. Turn around!FBI!
- 他們在哪? - 給我那玩意 我就告訴你們
- Give me the stuff, i'll tell you.
孩子們在哪?
Where are the kids?
什麼孩子?
What kids?
把他帶出去 他什麼都不知道
Get him out of here. He don't know nothin' else.
我們上去 來吧Rossi
We're going up. Come on,rossi.
安全!
Clear!
- 安全 - 安全
- Clear. - Clear.
Molly?
孩子們  我太抱歉了
The kids. I'm so sorry.
- 他們在哪? - 我不知道
- Where are they? - I don't know.
- 孩子們在哪? - 我不知道 你得找到他們
- Where are the kids? - I don't know. Find them.
- 好了 你會沒事的 - 我接住你了
- All right. You're gna be ok. - I got you.
好了
Ok.
安全!
Clear!
Rossi 嘿小男子漢 嘿 沒事了
Rossi. Hey,little man. Hey,it's ok.
沒事了
It's ok.
去找Muller
Go get muller.
你爸爸正在找你呢
Your dad's looking for you.
我們會把你從這弄出去的
We're gonna get you out of here.
會沒事的 好嗎? 我們現在就去找你爸爸了
It's gonna be ok, all right? We're getting your dad right now.
你沒事吧?
are you ok?
沒事
Ok.
嘿 你怎麼樣啊? 我能把你抱起來嗎? 好了 好了
How you doing? Can I pick you up? Ok. Ok.
到這來 甜心
Come here,sweetheart.
哦 我抱住你了
Oh,i got you.
(美國作家)華盛頓·歐文說過 "眼淚 有一種神聖的東西"
Washington irving said, "there is a sacredness in tears.
"它不是懦弱的標誌 而是力量的象徵"
"they are not the mark of weakness,but of power.
"它傳遞著無法承受的悲痛 以及無法言表的愛"
"they are messengers of overwhelming grief and of unspeakable love."
你有空嗎?
You got a sec?
進來吧
Come in.
我只是想說 對你小組的領導工作
I just wanted to say that you exceeded all expectations leadg this team.
超出了我的 還有其他人的所有期望
Mine and everyone else's.
你也是這樣的啊 Hotch
So have you,hotch.
你顯示出了一個與生俱來的 領導者的技巧和自信 還有...
You showed the skill and nfidence of a natal leader, and...
- 為此我謝謝你 - 我應該的
- I thank you for it. - Of course.
- 我懂你為什麼回來 - 你懂?
- Do you?
你永遠也不會安於 只坐在辦公桌後面 知道為什麼嗎?
You were never going to sit behind a desk. You know why?
因為 你兒子知道 你抓壞人
Because your son knows that you get the bad guys.
如果你不去試圖抓住他們 那兒子會怎麼想呢?
And if you're not out there trying to catch them, what's he going to think?
好吧 今晚他會想上床的時候我不在
Well,tonight he's gonna think I wasn't there at bedtime.
你是他的英雄 Hotch
You're his hero,hotch.
我 嗯...覺得我可以替你省幾個小時
I,uh,figured i'd save you a couple hours.
- 你沒有必要再做這個了 - 我知道我不用
- You don't have to do that anymore. - I know I don't.
但我也知道 在單親家庭 被撫養長大是什麼感覺
But I also know what it's like to be raised by a single parent.
每一分鐘都很重要
Every minute counts.
所以 如果你需要我一直這麼做 我再樂意不過了
So if you need me to make that a regular thing, i'd be more than happy to.
對此我很感激 真的
I appreciate that. I really do.
- 晚安 - 晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
犯罪心理 第五季 第11集 復仇
== 結束 ==
Criminal Minds Season05 Episode11 Retaliation